[{"id": 2855, "question": "Sure, it's good to get along with your teacher because it makes that time you spend in the classroom more pleasant. And yes, it's good to get along with your teacher because, in general, it's smart to learn how to relate to the different types of people you'll meet throughout your life. But really, there's one super-important reason why you should get along with your teacher. Kids who get along with their teachers not only learn more, but they're more comfortable asking questions and getting extra help. This makes it easier to understand new material and do your best on tests. When you have this kind of relationship with a teacher, he or she can be someone to turn to with problems, such as problems with learning or school issues, such as bullying. As a kid in elementary or middle school, y...\n\nQ: What's the writer's attitude towards getting along with teachers?", "options": ["Doubtful.", "Objective.", "Uncaring.", "Favorable."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2909, "question": "When I came to Cincinnati as an au pair , a lot of things there were different from what I knew. My host family lived in a huge house I could only describe as a \"castle\".In Germany I had lived in a small apartment together with my mom. Soon I found out that the \"castle\" was actually rather small in our neighborhood. Everybody there was very friendly and polite. They greeted you when they were walking by at least 3 feet away from you. They must not have seen a German au pair before, for most people I met asked me all kinds of questions about Germany. I enjoyed answering their various strange questions. I made a lot of friends and I started to hang out with them. Of course, there were a number of new things, and it took me the whole year to find them all out. I never got homesick. Perhaps it...\n\nQ: In the opinion of the author, life in Cincinnati was   _  .", "options": ["wonderful", "hard", "painful", "strange"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 388, "question": "A meteor that exploded over Russia's Ural mountains and sent burning to earth has set off a rush to find fragments of the space rock which hunters hope could fetch thousands of dollars a piece. Friday's explosion and following shockwave shattered windows, injured almost 1200 people and caused about $33 million worth of damage, said local authorities. It also started a \"meteorite rush\" around the industrial city of Chelyabinsk,where groups of people have started _ the snow and ice. \"The price is hard to say yet... The fewer meteorites that are discovered, the higher their price is.\" Said Dmitry Kachkalin, a member of the Russian Society of Amateur Meteorite Lovers. Meteorites are parts of a meteor that have fallen to earth. Scientists at the Urals Federal University were the first to announ...\n\nQ: Which of the following can best serve as the title of the passage?", "options": ["How to identity a meteorite", "To sell or to keep your meteorite", "Meteorite rush around Chelyabinsk", "Meteor explosion caused great damage"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 523, "question": "Runners in a relay race pass a stick in one direction. However, merchants passed silk, gold, fruit, and glass along the Silk Road in more than one direction. They earned their living by traveling the famous Silk Road. The Silk Road was not a simple trading network. It passed through thousands of citied and towns. It started from eastern China, across Central Asia and the Middle East, and ended in the Mediterranean Sea. It was used from about 200 B, C, to about A, D, 1300, when sea travel offered new routes , It was sometimes called the world's longest highway. However, the Silk Road was made up of many routes, not one smooth path. They passed through what are now 18 countries. The routes crossed mountains and deserts and had many dangers of hot sun, deep snow and even battles. Only experie...\n\nQ: It's probable that traders along the Silk Road needed  _  .", "options": ["to remember the entire trade route", "to know the making of products", "to receive certain special training", "to deal with a lot of difficulties"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 173, "question": "China has recently been faced with serious issues of product safety. In Panama, it is said that medicine made with a poisonous chemical sickened some people. A Chinese company had identified it as diethylamide glycol ( []), a low - cost substitute commonly used in automobile antifreeze . Some countries have banned Chinese-made toothpaste containing diethylamide glycol. China has now told companies to discontinue its use, even though it says the toothpaste is safe. Another industrial chemical, melamine, was found in wheat flour used to make pet food in North America. Thousands of dogs and cats became sick. The United States has restricted some imports of Chinese seafood because they contained banned substance. And questions have been raised about other products, including children's toys co...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["China is facing product safety problems", "more controls are taken of Chinese goods", "overstated problems with Chinese goods", "China is losing its trade partners"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3385, "question": "Life is too short to waste a moment, so while you still have time, let your hair down, remove that \"boring\" tag in your so-called life and start making it worthwhile. Below are some tips that will help you live a wonderful life. 1. Keep a Positive Attitude. Enjoy what you have and work on getting the things you desire. Psychologists believe that optimism is a good defense against unhappiness, so it is better to keep your optimism alive. Feeling sad about your life will only make you sadder, so be happy. 2. Don't Be Afraid to Take Risks. Life is all about taking risks, and that's the exciting part of it. Challenges and failure are part of life. Once you learn how to take risks, you'll soon realize how good it feels not to let moments pass you by. 3. You only have one life, so make it worthw...\n\nQ: What's the best title for the third tip?", "options": ["Enjoy Today and Let Go of the Past.", "Never Think of Tomorrow.", "Remember You Are the Best.", "Never Change Your Mind."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1349, "question": "Six seconds after its launch in Virginia, US, an unmanned rocket bound for the International Space Station (ISS) exploded, disappointing people both on Earth and in space. Hundreds of millions of dollars worth of cargo was destroyed in the Oct. 28 explosion due to An\"equipment failure\", said Orbital Sciences, the company hired by NASA for the resupply mission. The rocket was carrying a cargo ship loaded with 2,200 kilograms of supplies such as food, tools, parts, and experiments. Roughly a third of the cargo was a series of scientific investigations. Some of them were from high school students in the US. For example, 10 students from the Cristo Rey Jesuit College Preparatory School of Houston were conducting experiments about microgravity and put their samples on the rocket. \"I know that f...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE about the ISS, according to the article?", "options": ["Half of the astronauts at the ISS are from the US.", "The ISS was set up by four countries.", "The water that astronauts at the ISS drink is mainly made by recycling.", "Most of the food astronauts eat at the ISS is frozen and tastes bad."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1043, "question": "Children will find it more difficult to buy cigarettes as vending machines selling tobacco will be officially banned in England today.According to the British Heart Foundation(BHF),around 200,000 young people start smoking regularly in England each year and 11 per cent of l1-to15-year-old regular smokers in England and Wales get their cigarettes from vending machines. Betty McBride, Director of Policy and Communications at the British Heart Foundation,said,\"Thousands of children who are at risk of addiction regularly get tobacco from these machines,which of course,don't ask them to prove their age.With the tobacco industry increasingly depending on young smokers to keep their profits,they're fighting tooth and nail to stop any changes that might hit their bottom line.\" The ban, which makes...\n\nQ: The tobacco industry may be against the new regulation because   _", "options": ["more children will be at risk of tobacco addiction", "it will bring inconvenience to its consumers", "young smokers will be discouraged", "many vending machines will be left unused"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2278, "question": "It was 1961 and I was in the fifth grade. My marks in school were miserable and, the thing was, I didn't know enough to really care. My older bother and I lived with Mom in an ugly multi-family house in Detroit. We watched TV every night. The background noise of our lives was gunfire and horses' hoofs from \"Wagon Train\" or \"Cheyenne\", and laughter from\"I Love Lucy\", or\"Mister Ed\".After supper, we'd lie on Mom's bed and stare for hours at the TV screen. But one day Mom changed our world forever. She turned off the TV. Our mother had only been able to get through third grade. But, she was much brighter and smarter than we boys know at the time. She had noticed something in the suburban houses where she cleaned books. So she came home one day, switched off the TV, sat us down and explained th...\n\nQ: Which of the following is not true about the author's family?", "options": ["He came from a middle-class family.", "He came from a single-parent family.", "His mother worked as a cleaner.", "His mother had received little education."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 864, "question": "Most people who live in Seattle, Washington, love their city. There is a never-ending flow of fun things to do. But, people who live there do not always enjoy the day-after-day absence of sunshine during the winter months. It is documented fact that sunshine (or lack of it) plays a major role in how each of us meets the day. It also affects how we perform at school or work. When people are derived of sunlight, they can develop seasonal affective disorder, which makes it difficult for them to feel happy or get things accomplished. No major city in the United States is more affected by the \"sunshine factor\" than Seattle. To fight drizzle and fog during the winter months, Steve Murphy created a business that is very popular among the locals. The Indoor Sun Shoppe is more than a little ray of ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["Seattle is located in the state of Washington.", "Citizens love Seattle for their colorful city lives.", "Sunshine in Seattle is rare during the winter months.", "People who live in Seattle are used to the sunshine absence."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1227, "question": "A Russian,a Cuban,an American businessman and an American lawyer were on a train traveling across England. The Russian took out a large bottle of vodka, gave each of the men a drink and then threw the rest half bottle of vodka out of the window. \"Why did you do that?\" asked the American businessman. \"There's too much vodka in my country,\" said the Russian,\"And really we have more than we will ever use.\" A little later,the Cuban passed around fine Havana Cigars. Then he threw his out of the window. \"I thought Cuba is not a rich country,\" the businessman said. \"But you threw that very good cigars out of the window!\" \"Cigars,\" the Cuban answered,\"are the cheapest in my country. We have more of them than we know what to do with.\" The American businessman sat quietly for a moment. Then he got u...\n\nQ: When the businessman said \"I thought Cuba is not a rich country.\",he meant \"  _  \".", "options": ["Russian is richer than Cuba", "America is not richer than Cuba and Russia", "You shouldn't threw that very good cigar away", "Do you have more cigars than me?"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1396, "question": "Many people turn to doctors or self-help books, but they ignore a powerful thing that could help them fight illness: their friends. Researchers are only now starting to pay attention to the importance of friendship in health. A 10-year Australian study found that old People with a large circle of friends. A large 2007 study showed an increase of nearly 60 percent in the risk for obesity among people whose friends gained weight. And last year, Harvard researchers reported that strong social ties could improve brain health as we age. \" _ ,\" said Rebecca, a professor at the University of North Carolina. \" _ . \" While many friendship studies are about the close relationships of women, some research shows that it can do good to men too. In a six-year study of 736 middle-aged men, having friends...\n\nQ: The author mentioned smoking in the text to discuss  _  .", "options": ["the cause of heart attack.", "the risk of having no friends.", "smoking is bad for men.", "friends' influence on habits."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 560, "question": "The USA Well, imagine how my sister felt when she went off for the first time to New York for a business trip. After a few days she was still amazed at how friendly everyone was to her until she took a taxi back to her hotel one night. First she gave just the name of the hotel, but when asked she said the address too. Then she was asked how to get there, but of course she didn't know. Imagine how frightened she was when the driver started shouting at her for not knowing the way. The UK A friend was in London for a conference. He took a taxi and there were no problems: the driver knew the way and was very cheerful. The problem started when he realized he had stupidly left his laptop on the back seat! He called the company up and, in a panic, went straightaway to their Lost and Found office....\n\nQ: What was the author's sister's trip by taxi in the US like?", "options": ["Unpleasing and scary.", "Tiring but impressive.", "Relaxing and exciting.", "Interesting but strange"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 147, "question": "Growing up in Philadelphia, Lieberman started cooking with his stay-at-home dad when he was seven. His food-loving family had two kitchens, and he quickly learned what was the best way to bake his cakes. Lieberman improved his kitchen skills during a year abroad beforo college, learning from a cook in Italy and study local specialties in Gerrnany, Spain and France. At Yale,he was known for throwing dinner parties, single-handedly frying and baking while mixing drinks for dozens offriends. Just for fun, he and some friends decided to tape a show named Campus Cuisine about his cooking. Lieberman was a real college student showing his classmate how to do things like making drinks out of dining-hall fruit. That helped the show become very popular among the students. They would stop Lieberman a...\n\nQ: What does the word\"charisma\" underline in the text refer to ?", "options": ["A natural ability to attract others.", "A way to show one's achievement.", "Lieberman's after-class interest", "Lieberman's fine cooking skill"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2130, "question": "The management and staff are happy to welcome you and will do all they can to make your stay an enjoyable one. We hope you will find the following suggestions and information of use to you. MEAL TIMES Our overnight charge includes a continental-type breakfast. Breakfast: 7:30-9:30 a. m. Lunch: 12:00-2:00 p. m. Afternoon tea: 4:00-5:30 p. m. Dinner: 7:00-9:15 p. m. Meals can be served in rooms at a small extra charge. We regret that owing to staff arrangements, meals cannot be served outside these times. In exceptional circumstances please consult one of our receptionists in advance. Light refreshments, including tea, coffee, biscuits and sandwiches, can be served in rooms between 10:00 a. m. and 11:00 p. m. except during the meal times listed above. Cold drinks are available in the room re...\n\nQ: Where is this notice most likely to be found?", "options": ["At restaurants.", "In shops.", "In hotels.", "In the newspapers."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3424, "question": "Discover Newsmagazine of science devoted to the wonders and stories of modern science, written for the educated general reader. Published by Disney Magazine Publishing Co., Discover tells many of the same stories professionals read in Scientific American. A truly delightful family science magazine, each issue brings to light new and newsworthy topics to make dinnertime and water-cooler conversations interesting. Cover Price: $59.88 Price: $19.95 ($1.66/issue) You Save: $39.93 (67%) Issues: 12 issues/12 months Self Published by Conde Nast Publications Inc., Self is a handbook devoted to women's overall physical and mental health. Every issue contains usable articles such as \"Style Lab\", in which wearable clothes are mixed and matched on non-models and the \"Eat-right Road Map\", with tips on ...\n\nQ: Which of the following magazines is published monthly?", "options": ["Discover.", "Self.", "InStyle.", "Wired."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 490, "question": "WILD WEATHERMAN Name: Sam Champion Hot job: TV Weatherman Where: ABC-TV, New York City When you were a child, did you plan to forecast wind, rain, and snow on TV? I wanted to be a foreign journalist. I took courses in weather science at Eastern Kentucky University, but I majored in broadcasting news. How did you finally become a weatherman? My first job in the early 1980s was at the local TV station in Paducah, Kentucky. I did everything from turning on the lights in the morning to writing and delivering morning news. I put together weather forecasts, and became interested in them. Back then, how did you forecast weather? Independent companies collected computer information that showed, for example, how a single weather system might split into snow or snow mixed with rain. The information ...\n\nQ: As a child, ABC-TV's Sam Champion wanted to be a   _   .", "options": ["space scientist", "weatherman", "news reporter", "meteorologist"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 82, "question": "The best selling children's book, Pipilu Sending You 100 Lives, has been adapted into a homonymous play that will be put on for the first time next March and tour around 50 cities in China. The book was adapted by the Hangzhou based Star Dream Factory. \"We don't want to descend to the average children's dramas that are overly eager to please the kids,\" said Huang Qin, director of Star Dream Factory. \"We want to provide something practically useful and mystically entertaining.\" The original book by Chinese children's book writer Zheng Yuanjie focuses on safety tips for kids. With Zheng's usual _ and simplicity, the book avoids sugar-coating reality. Instead, it illustrates the potential dangers in everyday life and provides possible solutions. Zheng recalled that when he saw his new-born ba...\n\nQ: According to Zheng,safety   _  .", "options": ["is more important to people than any other things", "is an essential part only to all the children", "is more important to the old than the young", "is more important to the young than the old"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1886, "question": "Teen Dating can be fun if you are aware of its pros and cons and are also aware of the ways to protect yourself. There are a couple of suggestions you would like to know before you are out for dating. Do not go out for dating with somebody whom you have seen only a few times and does not know much about him or her. Before leaving on a date, know the exact plans for the evening and make sure a parent or friend knows these plans and what time to expect you home. Let your date know that you are expected to call or tell that person when you get in. Similarly, if you leave a party with someone you do not know well, make sure you tell another person you are leaving and with whom. Ask a friend to call and make sure you arrive home safely. No matter how good the person appears to you, trust your i...\n\nQ: If you feel uncomfortable, you should NOT  _", "options": ["leave as soon as possible", "tell your date what you are thinking", "stay calm", "trust yourself"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3082, "question": "Wild animals seem to have escaped the Indian Ocean tsunami , adding weight to ideas they possess a \"sixth sense\" for disasters, experts said on Thursday. Sri Lanka wildlife officials have said the giant waves that killed over 24,000 people along the Indian Ocean island's coast seemingly missed wild beasts, with no dead animals found. \"No elephants are dead, not even a dead hare or rabbit. I think animals can sense disaster. They have a sixth sense. They know when things are happening,\" H.D. Ratnayake, deputy director of Sri Lanka's Wildlife Department, said on Wednesday. The waves washed floodwaters up to 3 km (2 miles) inland at Yala National Park in the southeast, Sri Lanka's biggest wildlife reserve and home to hundreds of wild elephants. \"There has been a lot of evidence about dogs bar...\n\nQ: This passage is mainly about  _  .", "options": ["the damage that was caused in the Indian Ocean tsunami", "why animals can save them from natural disasters", "how to protect the wildlife when disaster happens", "the different opinions about animals' natural power"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3272, "question": "If you have been joining in chat room conversations, or trading email with web pals , you have become one of the millions who write in a peculiarly short form of English. And you've got a sense of humor about short forms like SOHF (=\" sense\" of humor failure) to describe Internet newcomers who don't understand you. Across the globe, every night teenagers and their elders are \"talking online\", many of them all talking at the same time. It's fast: try talking to six people at once.It's brief: three or four words per exchange.It takes wit, concentration, and quick fingers. And it requires tremendous linguistic economy .There's neither time nor space for explanations.Why consume precious key-strokes telling six friends you have to leave for a moment to take care of your little brother when BRB...\n\nQ: To save time on the Internet,    _   .", "options": ["some people leave their letters in the dustbin", "some people never use \"shift\" in their writing", "many people leave the capital and punctuation", "people seldom use capital letters or punctuation"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 71, "question": "A new study has been carried to test the role of story telling in lowering blood pressure. Dr. Thomas Houston, a professor of the University of Massachusetts Medical School, led a group of scientists that investigated how pre-recorded videos of hypertension patients' talking about their medical histories helped another group of patients with high blood pressure to control their condition over several months. Houston was surprised by their studies that suggested that communication can be a powerful tool in medicine. They showed that those who had had similar experiences, when talking to someone with a similar background, could help change their behavior to become healthier. Hypertension is difficult to control, since it is dependent on diet, exercise and mental state. Medical treatments wit...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that the pre-recorded videos   _  .", "options": ["tell medical histories of hypertension patients", "introduce some medical treatments of hypertension", "introduce a good lifestyle for hypertensive patients", "tell scientific discoveries of the scientist group"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3110, "question": "In the 1960s, people asked about your astrological sign . In the 1990s, they wanted to know your website. These days, having a web address is almost as important as a street address. Your website is an electronic meeting place for your family, friends and potentially, millions of people around the world. Best of all, you may not have to spend a cent. The Web is filled with all kinds of free services and all it takes is some time and creativity. Think of your home page as the starting point of your website. Like the table of contents of a book or a magazine, the home page is the front door. Your site can have one or more pages, depending on how you design it. While web pages vary greatly in their design and content, most use a traditional magazine layout. At the top of the page is a banner ...\n\nQ: The purpose of the home page of your website is   _  .", "options": ["to give a list of all the contents of your website", "to make it look like a front door", "to direct people to more of your pages", "to design the cover of a book or magazine"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1956, "question": "In today's throw away society, dealing with the city's growing mountain of waste is an inereasing challenge for the city countil . Recently. Edinburgh is faced with the problem of dssposing of about250,000 Million tons of waster a year . Despite different ways to dispose of much of it in a green manner---largely through encouraging tecycling---its aging facilities such as the Powderhall landfill do not have the ability to deal with it. The European Union(EU) has issued a new policy, regulating how such mountains of waster are to hr disposed of. The five councils (Edinburgh. East Lothian. West Lothian. Midlethian and Borders) face fine around $18million a year from 2013 it they don't inerease recycling levels and rely less on landfill. With this in mind, the coumlls got together with the id...\n\nQ: The main way of handling waste in a green manmer in Edinburgh is_.", "options": ["recyeling", "restoring", "burying", "burning"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 829, "question": "Among the many differences between Western and Chinese cultures, table manners are one of the most noticeable differences. Westerners often make mistakes at the table in China or in a Chinese home. In order not to have an embarrassing experience, here are some things to consider next time you are eating with some Chinese. Step1: Keep in mind that food is shared. It is one of the biggest differences between Chinese and Western eating habits. In China a few dishes are placed in the center of a table and shared by all. Also, you should offer thanks when a Chinese host takes food from one of the dishes on the table and places it on your plate. Refusing it would not be polite even if you are full. Step2: Respect the chopsticks. The chopsticks are the single most important tool at a Chinese tabl...\n\nQ: How can you use your chopsticks according to the passage?", "options": ["Use them to grab your own food.", "Put them on the table.", "Use them to skewer the food.", "Stick them into the rice bowl."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2060, "question": "The vast jungles of the Amazon rainforest are home to tribes mostly isolated from the outside world,whose way of life,largely unchanged for hundreds of years,is now increasingly threatened by modern civilization. Now, scientists discover they can monitor these\"uncontacted tribes\"using satellites,which would allow inexpensive and safe tracking of these tribes in order to protect them from outside threats. In order to help conserve these uncontacted Indians,researchers need accurate estimates of their populations.One way to collect this data involves flying over their villages,but such overflights are both expensive and could fill these native peoples with fear.Another strategy involves meeting individuals on the ground,but among other risks,scientists could accidentally spread disease to me...\n\nQ: What do scientists find about the tribes?", "options": ["They live close together.", "Their population is dropping.", "Thev live in distributed areas.", "Their population is increasing fast."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2413, "question": "Every language has its own special words and expressions. And a story can be told about each of them. \"Hot\" is a simple, easily-understood word. So are most of the expressions made with the word \"hot\". But not always, as we shall see. Take the phrase \"hot potato\" for example. The potato is a popular vegetable in the United States. Many people like baked potatoes, cooked in an oven or fire. Imagine trying to carry a hot, baked potato in your hand. It would be difficult, even painful, to do so. One such hot potato is taxes. Calling for higher taxes can mean defeat for a politician. And yet, if taxes are not raised, some very popular government programs could be cut, which can also make a politician very unpopular. Another expression is \"not so hot\". If you ask someone how she feels, she may ...\n\nQ: The purpose of the first hot line was   _  .", "options": ["to stop the Cold War", "to prevent accidental war between the two superpowers", "to promote the cooperation between the Soviet Union and the United States", "to make direct telephone links for the people in Moscow and Washington"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1687, "question": "Americans often say that there are only two things a person can be sure of:death and taxes.Many people feel that the United States has the worst taxes in the world. Taxes are the money that people pay to support their government.There are generally three levels of government in the United States:federal,state,and city;therefore,there are three types of taxes. Salaried people who can earn more than four to five thousand dollars per year must pay a certain part.It depends on their salaries.The federal government has a two-level income tax:that is,15 or 28 percent.$17 850 is the cut off.The tax rate is 15 percent below $17 850 and 28 percent above. The second tax is for the state government:New York,California,or any of the other forty-eight states.Some states have an income tax similar to th...\n\nQ: What tax does an American have to pay to the city if he owns a car?", "options": ["Property tax.", "Excise tax.", "Income tax.", "Sales tax."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1839, "question": "One rainy night , Mark decided to end his life . Having undergone a lot of sufferings and frustrations , he walked the streets , feeling desperate . On that same night , I was sitting in my room when I heard the doorbell rang . My mom opened the door , finding herself face-to-face with a very disheveled-looking man , Mark , with tears running down his face . My mom , overcome by pity , invited him inside . Curious , I went downstairs to get a better look . The sight of the man , holding his head in his hands and crying , made my chest ache . I raced back upstairs to my room , pulled out my only half-dollar coin from my money jar and ran back downstairs . When I reached the door of the living room , I walked right in and quickly made my way over to the stranger . I put the half-dollar in hi...\n\nQ: Mom let Mark inside our house because she   _   .", "options": ["was hospitable to anyone", "was ready to help others", "wanted to educate me", "felt sorry for him"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1058, "question": "They may be small and not able to speak, but babies are proving their amazing cleverness. Scientists began finding infants' skills are more than they are supposed to be. _ Speaking of music, babies can't seem to resist it. Not only are their ears turned to the beats, babies can actually dance to the music. To test babies' dancing ability, the researchers played recordings of classical music, rhythmic beats and speech to infants, and recorded the results. They also invited professional dancers to analyze how well the babies matched their movements to the music. The babies moved their arms, hands, legs feet and heads in response to the music, much more than to the speech. The finding suggests this dancing ability is innate in humans, though the researchers aren't sure why _ becomes weaker la...\n\nQ: In the last experiment, most babies chose the helper character, showing that  _  .", "options": ["babies can judge a person helpful or harmful", "babies love to see a puppet show", "babies were born to help others", "babes have learned to help others"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1952, "question": "\"It was cool,because I got a chance to be in a studio and see how a record is made,\"says 14-year-old Javon Martin,who joined the music clubhouse 3 years ago.\"It has impacted my life in a big way. People are actually starting to see me as an artist.\"Ten-year-old Akheylah Hunter didn't play an instrument when she became a club member last year. Now,she plays piano and sings with the band. What she likes best,she says,is performing.\"We performed in different places,\"she says.\"We go on trips and it is fun.\" Since the Music Clubhouse opened three years ago,it's served almost 500 kids.Aggeler says performing in front of different audiences helps the young musicians build self-esteem.Coming to the club to prepare for those performances helps them learn how to deal with their personal problems and...\n\nQ: Which of the following might NOT be included in activities of the club?", "options": ["Putting on performances.", "Making records.", "Traveling to different places.", "Giving private music lessons."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2108, "question": "Ann was on her first package trip in Rosas, Spain. At the hotel, she checked in, and then went to her room to change before dinner. She was just ready to go downstairs when she found that her Spanish money wasn't in her handbag. She carefully looked in all her luggage, but she couldn't find it. All she had was a small purse with ten English pound notes in it! Ann found a place to change her English money. She had very few pesetas , and she would be here for two weeks. On her way back to the hotel, Ann bought some cheese, some bread and some oranges. When she got back, she told the manager that her doctor had told her not to eat Spanish food; she'd just have breakfast each day. That was all right, as she knew the price of hotels included breakfast. For the rest of her holiday, Ann swam in t...\n\nQ: Why did Ann buy some cheese, some bread and some oranges?", "options": ["Because they were good for her health.", "Because she is afraid that she couldn't eat enough in the hotel restaurant.", "Because she liked them more than dinners in the hotel restaurant.", "Because she planned to eat them instead of lunch and supper."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1984, "question": "Why are so many students not doing well? Why is there such a huge achievement gap between urban and suburban students? Just this week, in my school the seventh grade team leader called a meeting to discuss academic detention . The purpose of the detention is to allow students who are doing poorly a second chance to redo the work. Now if a student did not understand an assignment I have no trouble allowing that student to redo a test or give some extra credit work, but if a student did poorly because he/she opted not to do the work out of sheer laziness, that student should not be given a second chance. And parents should be held accountable for their children. That is another reason why there is such a huge achievement gap. All children should be monitored at home in order to achieve great...\n\nQ: The author believes that a student can be given a second chance   _  .", "options": ["if he did poorly the first time", "for whatever reason he did poorly the first time", "if he failed the first time in spite of his efforts", "if he comes from a suburban area"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1923, "question": "Ad.1 West High School Bake Sale Come and support our band and buy some delicious baked goods! Friday, September 20th, 2:00 - 4:00 p.m. In the hall by the office after school Cookies: 25 cents each or 5 for $1 Brownies: 50 cents each or 3 for $1.25 Cake by the slice: $1 Whole cakes: $8 Proceeds go toward sending our band to Nationals. Ad.2 SHIPPING AND HANDLING CHARGES Ups or U.S. Parcel Post are the standard methods for continental U.S. shipments. ORDER TOTAL GROUND EXPEDITED GROUND 9-12 working days 4-5 working days $0.00 to $30.00 $4.50 $5.50 $30.01 to $60.00 $7.25 $8.25 $60.01 to $100.00 $9.50 $10.50 $100.01 to $200.00 $11.50 $12.50 Add $7.00 to Ground Rates for 3 Days....\n\nQ: Which of the following gives you the most for your money if you buy the baked goods?", "options": ["4 cookies.", "5 cookies.", "2 brownies", "One slice of cake."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1444, "question": "Anyone who doubts that children are born with a healthy amount of ambition need spend only a few minutes with a baby eagerly learning to walk. No matter how many times the little ones stumble in their first efforts, most keep on trying, determined to master their amazing new skill. It is only several years later, many psychologists and teachers agree, that a good number of kids seem to lose their natural drive to succeed. For the parents of such kids, whose own ambition is often tied to their children's success, it can be a painful experience. Figuring out why _ is the first step. Assuming that a kid doesn't suffer from a learning disability, or isn't involved in some family crisis at home, many educators attribute a sudden lack of motivation to a fear of failure or classmate pressure. \"Ev...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the parents of kids with no ambition  _  .", "options": ["don't do a very good job teaching them to walk", "are to blame if the kids do poorly in school", "feel pain because ambitions are connected to their success", "should take part in extra-curriculum activities with kids"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1326, "question": "City farms are gaining popularity in cities and towns around the United States. City Farms in Edmonston, Maryland, is located near shopping centers, car repair shops and homes. The neighborhood is a working-class community. People do not have very much money, and they have limited access to fresh food in markets. Over the past two years, the farm has attracted volunteers from the community like Marcy Clark. She schools her four children at home. On a recent day she brought them to Eco City Farms for a lesson. Alston Clark thinks his experience very valuable. \"I like coming out here, \"he says, \"You know, you connect with the earth, where your food comes from. You appreciate the food a little bit more. \" Margaret Morgan-Hubbard started Eco City Farms. She thinks of it as a place where people...\n\nQ: What is the author's attitude towards City Farms?", "options": ["Doubtful.", "Enthusiastic.", "Amazed.", "Negative."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1811, "question": "A 13-year-old American boy on Saturday became the youngest climber to conquer Mount Everest, the world's highest mountain. Jordan Romero from Big Bear, California, climbed up the 8,850-meter summit from the Tibetan side. On the same day, a Nepali man, Apa Sherpa, broke his own world record of climbing Everest when he reached the summit for the twentieth time. Apa Shepa's team set off from Nepal's capital, Kathmandu, last month, heading for the base camp on the Chinese side of the mountain. \"The team has just called in and believe that they are standing on top of Mt. Everest,\" Romero's blog said. \"Their dreams have now come true. Everyone is happy.\" The climbing has put Romero one step closer to reaching his goal of climbing the highest mountains on all seven continents . \"It is just a goal...\n\nQ: To stand on the highest mountains on all seven continents, Jordan Romero plans to climb the peak in   _  .", "options": ["Asia", "Antarctica", "Europe", "Africa"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3462, "question": "Manage your time well for each module , but also make sure you get a good balance between work and social life. That is for life in general. Set aside time specifically for each subject. Try to study one subject a day. You need to balance time. If you are bad at balancing things, make a personal timetable. Even if you do not stick to it, you will have an idea what you should be doing each day. This is better than trying to do everything each day and, at the end of the week, not achieve anything. Also, try to keep your weekends free of studying. Only study at the weekend if you really have to. I had to learn to balance work, study and family when I was at college. I was a retail assistant working part-time and had at least four modules to complete at the same time at college. I also had to ...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about?", "options": ["I had a good time during my college.", "How to study well at college.", "Balance time between study and other aspects of your life.", "How to plan your things in advance."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3483, "question": "A few years ago, I moved into a new house in Los Angeles. Soon after, a family moved in next door. It wasn't the best of times for me. I had just divorced from my second wife, and I wasn't working. I'd come home each day and sit by myself in the backyard. One night, I heard someone from the yard next door, \"Tom ! How are you, Tom? \" I couldn't see anybody through the trees, but I answered, \"I' m good.\" \"Good!\" said the voice. \"What's your name?\" I asked. \"Eric.\" Then I heard someone say, \"Eric, don't bother him.\" \"Okay!\" Eric said. \"Talk to you tomorrow!\" Months later, on Halloween, we finally met face to face. Eric came to the door dressed like a rap star. We became friends. We'd hang out in our yards, and Eric, who was almost 17 at the time and look liked a 13-year-old, would tell me his...\n\nQ: From his experience in Los Angeles, the writer learnt that_.", "options": ["where there is a will, there is a way.", "one should always learn from the past.", "one can find opportunity anywhere.", "life can always be better."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 850, "question": "Even if you are a good high-jumper, you can jump only about seven feet off the ground. You cannot jump any higher because the earth pulls you hard. The pull of the earth is called gravity. You can easily find out the pull of the earth. If you weigh yourself, you will know how much gravity is pulling you. Since there is gravity, water runs down hill. When you throw a ball into the air, it falls back down. Because of gravity, you do not fall off the earth as it whirls around. Then, can we get away from the earth and go far out into space? Now you can do it, because spaceships have been invented. Then spaceship will go so fast that it can escape the earth's gravity and carry you into space....\n\nQ: Because of gravity,  _", "options": ["water flows everything.", "we can go everywhere by ship.", "water always flows downwards.", "fish can live in water."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 368, "question": "Every few years, two groups carry out a study of how many Americans wash their hands after using the toilet. These groups are the American Society for Microbiology and the American Cleaning Institute, formerly the Soap and Detergent Association. There was good news in the latest study. Researchers found that eighty-five percent of adults washed their hands in public restrooms last month. That was the most since the studies began in 1996. Researchers visited restrooms at a baseball park in Atlanta and a science museum and aquarium in Chicago. They also visited two train stations in New York City and a large farmers' market in San Francisco. In all, they observed about six thousand adults, with females and males equal in number. The researchers found that seventy-seven percent of men and nin...\n\nQ: According to the latest study, about  _  women washed their hands after using public bathroom.", "options": ["1,980", "2,310", "2,640", "2,790"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2614, "question": "Matt grow the best vegetables in the village.He grows fruit too--big , sweet apples and oranges.And what else ? Well , the biggest and the prettiest flowers.Things grow in Matt' s garden all through the year.He cuts some flowers for his sitting room table ; and of course , he eats some fruit and vegetables.But he sells everything else in the market.Matt is not a poor man. He knows a few other gardens ; but he does not have any friends.You might ask , \" What is that ? Why doesn ' t he have friends ? \" I will tell you.People do not understand him.And they do not understand his garden, \" Why not ? \" you will ask.\" It' s a very good garden , isn' t it ? \" It is a wonderful garden.Matt plants things in spring , summer and autumn and winter .After that he does very little work.He sits in the gar...\n\nQ: People don' t like Matt because    _   .", "options": ["he doesn' t give thim any vegetables or fruit", "he listens to the radio too much", "they are jealous of him", "Matt doesn' t let them listen to his radio"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1245, "question": "Billy's favorite color is orange. But he can't see what orange looks like. Billy is blind. A month after he was born, his mother noticed that his eyes weren't quite as big as a normal baby's.\"Billy would never be able to see.\" the doctor told his mother. After that Billy's mother began talking to him, describing things she saw outside the window. She described everything to him. Billy does not only depend on his mother's descriptions to learn about the world around him. He sees with his ears and his hands, too. He has perfect hearing. When people make phone calls, he can tell the numbers they dial . Billy loves computer science. He began teaching himself computer programming when he was just seven years old. His dream school would be Stanford University. He gets top grades in his classes, ...\n\nQ: From the passage, we know that  _", "options": ["Billy can't hear.", "Billy can't see.", "Billy can't walk.", "Billy can't talk."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 644, "question": "Earthquakes are something that people fear. There are some places that have few or no earthquakes. Most places in the world, however, have them regularly . Countries that have a lot of earthquakes are usually quite mountainous. The most talked about earthquake in the United States was in San Francisco in 1906. Over 700 people died in it. The strongest one in North America was in 1964. It happened in Alaska. Strong earthquakes are not always the ones that kill the most people. In 1755, one of the strongest earthquakes ever recorded was felt in Portugal. Around 2,000 people died. In 1923, a very strong earthquake hit Tokyo, the Yokohama area of Japan. A hundred and forty thousand people died. Most of them died in fires which followed the earthquake. One of the worst earthquakes ever was in C...\n\nQ: How many people died in the earthquake which happened in Portugal in 1755?", "options": ["500.", "140,000.", "400,000.", "2,000."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2070, "question": "Five-year-old Jocelyn Rojas spent all day playing happily with her friends outside her grandmother's apartment building. Her mom, Jaimee, kept her eye on the little girl from a window. At about 4 p.m., Jocelyn walked around the corner of the building to get her bicycle. However, half an hour later, she disappeared. Jaimee called 911. A short time later, police officers and firefighters crowded inthe area, blocking streets and searching the neighborhood. Officers handed out photos of the girl wearing thick-framed glasses. Temar Boggs, 15, a school athlete in track, was with some friends moving a couch into the apartment of his elderly neighbor when one officer approached him and asked if he'd seen Jocelyn. Unfortunately, none of them had seen her. A little bit later, Temar and his friends w...\n\nQ: Why did Jaimee call 911?", "options": ["Because her mother was in need of help.", "Because her house was on fire.", "Because her daughter was missing.", "Because she was trapped in the building."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3081, "question": "C.O.P.D blocks air flow through the lungs. It makes breathing difficult. The leading cause of C.O.P.D. is cigarette smoking. Experts at the National Institutes of Health in the United States say there is no cure to the damage to the lungs. Dawn Demeo is an assistant professor at Harvard Medical School in Boston, Massachusetts. She said, \"By 2020, C.O.P.D. may be the third leading cause of death across the world.\" C.O.P.D. is a new name for emphysema and chronic bronchitis . These are the two most common forms of the disease. Many people with C.O.P.D. have both of them. And Doctor Demeo says more women than men now die from the disease. She is the lead author of a study by a team from Harvard's Brigham and Women's Hospital and the University of Bergen in Norway. The new study adds to findin...\n\nQ: In which part of a newspaper would you most probably read this passage?", "options": ["Science", "Health report", "Education", "Business report"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3179, "question": "NOT all math skills are learned in the classroom. Some of them come naturally. Consider the split-second calculations you make when you estimate the number of empty seats on the school bus or the number of cookies in a cookie jar. These estimates can often be done without counting. That's because humans are born with the ability to closely guess the number of items in a group. Researchers call this ability a person's \"number sense\". To see how a person's inborn number sense might be linked to mathematical performance in the classroom, psychologist Justin Halberda and his colleagues from Johns Hopkins University in prefix = st1 /Baltimore,USran some tests. The scientists asked 64 14-year-olds to look at images of yellow and blue dots that flashed on a computer screen for a fraction of a sec...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the most important thing to learn math well is that_.", "options": ["one should have an inborn number sense", "one should practice a lot", "one should do a lot of tests", "one should do a lot of counting"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2691, "question": "Teresa was born in Yugoslavia on August 27,1910. Her parents were Albanians and member of the Roman Catholic Church. When she was seven years old, her father was murdered. She decided not to be filled with hate because of this tragedy . Instead, she would seek a life of love. This ambition led her to Ireland where she became a nun at the age of eighteen. After only one year of training, she was sent to India to teach in a school called Loretto House, where the students were mostly from rich Indian families. After 15 years there, she left her duties as a teacher to \"follow Christ into the slums .\" Her heart led her away from the rich to the needs of the poor. She was then 36 years old. Teresa no longer was affiliated with the Irish nuns who sent her to Loreto House but worked independently....\n\nQ: Which of the following is WRONG?", "options": ["Mother Teresa was a Catholic.", "\"Sari\" is an Indian word that means clothing.", "At first people didn't believe her motives.", "She served poor people in the slums as a teacher."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2334, "question": "How do you get a man to do his share of the house work? If you are like most of the women, you will face the question the hard way. A man will enjoy a clean, orderly house, but he usually won't make the effort to clean or organize it. This doesn't mean that a woman has to do all the housework; she may have to manage many of household duties, and request his partner's participation. A woman can often say that men and women should take equal responsibility for housework. Very few men are raised to be fully responsible for housework, and many men look on housework as women's work. On the other hand, most men will readily work around the yard, make repairs and complete projects on weekends or evenings, and it's important that you give your man appreciation for those things too. Most man will t...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about how to   _  .", "options": ["get men to do some housework", "get men to serve their families", "praise men's housework", "make men do all the housework."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2915, "question": "Most young people enjoy some forms of physical activities. It may be walking, cycling or swimming, or in winter, skating or skiing. It may be a game of some kind, football, hockey, golf, or tennis, it may be mountaineering. Those who have a passion for climbing high and difficult mountains are often looked upon with astonishment. Why are men and women willing to suffer cold and hardship, and to take risks on high mountaineering? This astonishment is caused probably by the difference between mountaineering and other forms of activity to which men give their leisure. Mountaineering is a sport and not a game. There are no manmade rules, as there are for such game as golf and football. There are, of course, rules of a different kind, which would be dangerous to ignore, but it is this freedom f...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE?", "options": ["Mountaineers compete against nature.", "Mountaineers compete against teams.", "Mountaineers compete against each other.", "Mountaineers compete against international standard."], "answer": 0}]